Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Non-Target Countries, 1985-1990
  - African Development Fund. (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Senegal, 1985-1990
  - E.N.D.A. (Box 59, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial information - 08007. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 08007. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 08007. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Reports - 08007. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - O.E.F. (Box 59, Folder 5-12)
    - Reports - 08008. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 08008. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Unfoldered material - "M'Bao Women's Fish Processing Enterprise - Summary report" [black-covered report]., October 31, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - 08008. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Project summary - 08008. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 08009. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - 08009. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 08009. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) (Box 59, Folder 13-15)
    - Correspondence - 08010. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 08010. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 08010. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Terre des Homes (Box 59, Folder 16-18)
    - Correspondence - 08011. (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 08011. (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 08011. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Conseil des Organisations Non Gouvernmentales d'Appui au Developpement (CONGAD) (Box 59, Folder 19-24)
    - Correspondence - 08012. (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Project summary - 08012. (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 08012. (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - 08013. (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 08013. (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 08013. (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Association Culturelle d'Aide la Promotion Educative Sociale (ACAPES)/F.O.N.G. (Box 59, Folder 25-27)
    - Financial information - 08014. (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - 08014. (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - 08014. (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Senegal / Sudan, 1985-1990
  - Juenes de Quinotte (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence - 08015. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 08015. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 08015. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Association Nationale des Maisons Familiales Rurales (ANMFR) (Box 60, Folder 4-6)
    - Correspondence - no.08704. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - no.08704. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - no.08704. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - D.E.V.S.O.L. (Box 60, Folder 7-9)
    - Correspondence - no.08705. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - no.08705. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - no.08705. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - World relief (Box 60, Folder 10-13)
    - Reports - 08016 [empty]. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 08016. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - 08016. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 08016. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Conseil des Organisations Non Gouvernmentales d'Appui au Developpement (CONGAD) - no.UD8101. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - World vision (Box 60, Folder 15-19)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 08301. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Procurement - 08301. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Budget - 08301. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - 08301. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - World vision - Report - 08301. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Senegal (Box 60, Folder 20-23)
    - Country background. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Unfoldered material - OEF International. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - General information. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) - emergency medical assistance - 09202. (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Goal Sudan (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence - 09203. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 09203. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Budget - 09203. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Report - 09203. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (Box 60, Box 61)
    - Emergency medical kits for West Sudan - 09201. (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Unfoldered material - emergency refugee assistance in Southern Sudan/Uganda - 09204. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Emergency refugee assistance in Southern Sudan/Uganda - 09204. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University/Gorosh. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Old information - Columbia - 09301. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Unfoldered Material. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - M.V.I. (Box 61, Box 62)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 09302. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - 09302. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Budget - 09302. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Report - 09302. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Unfoldered material - Child survival project - 09302B. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University (Box 62, Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence - 09303. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Payment schedule - 09303 [half of manila folder]. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 09303. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Budget - 09303. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Reports (B). (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Reports (A). (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - World University Service-Canada (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
    - Water survey team: feasibility - 09308. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Unfoldered material - Water survey team: feasibility - 09308. (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Sudan, 1985-1990
  - Columbia University (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
    - Procurement (A and B) - 09303. (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - Improving Primary Health Care Project Management - no.09303. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Report - no.09303. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - American Refugee Committee (Box 63, Box 64)
    - Fau 5 - no.09309. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Safawa - no.09310. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - M.T.F. - no.09305. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Unfoldered material - Medical Training and Health Education Program - no.09305. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - International Rescue Committee (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
    - Sudan - no.09304. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Sudan - Procurement - no.09304. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Sudan - Reports. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Concern Sudan - no.09306 & no.09307. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Adventist Development and Relief Agency (ADRA) (Box 64, Folder 8-11)
    - Correspondence - no.09401. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - no.09401. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Project Summary - no.09401. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Progress Report - no.09401. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Yei District (Box 64, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - no.09402. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - no.09402. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Project Summary - no.09402. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Progress Report - no.09402 [empty]. (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Lalmba (Box 65, Folder 1-12)
    - Correspondence - no.09404. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - no.09404. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Project Summary - no.09404. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Progress Report - no.09404. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - no.09405. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - no.09405. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Project Summary - no.09405. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Progress Report - no.09405 [empty]. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - no.09406. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - no.09406. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Project Summary - no.09406. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Progress Report - no.09406 [empty]. (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - N.P.O. (Box 65, Folder 13-16)
    - Correspondence - no.09408. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Project Summary - no.09408. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - no.09408. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Progress Report - no.09408. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. (Box 65, Folder 17-25)
    - Correspondence - no.09409. (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - no.09409. (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Project Summary - no.09409. (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Progress Report - no.09409. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Unfoldered material. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - no.09410. (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Project Summary - no.09410. (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - no.09410. (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Progress Report - no.09410. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Sudan Council of Voluntary Agencies (Sudan Council of Voluntary Agencies (SCOVA) (Box 65, Box 66)
    - Correspondence - no.09411. (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Financial information - no.09411. (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Project Summary - no.09411. (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - S.C.O.V.A. / S.C.C. - Progress Report - no.09411. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - S.A.A. (Box 66, Folder 2-5)
    - Correspondence - no.09412. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - no.09412. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Project Summary - no.09412. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Progress Report - no.09412. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - S.J.C.O. (Box 66, Folder 6-10)
    - Correspondence - no.09413. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - no.09413. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Project Summary - no.09413. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Progress Report - no.09413. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Old Proposals - no.09413. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - I.A.R.A. (Box 66, Folder 11-14)
    - Correspondence - no.09414. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Financial information - no.09414. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Project Summary - no.09414. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Joint Family Health Care Programme - Khartoum/Sudan - Progress Report. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Far (Box 66, Folder 15-21)
    - Correspondence - no.09001. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - no.09001. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Project Summary - no.09001. (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Progress Report - no.09001. (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - no.09002. (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - no.09002. (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Project Summary - no.09002. (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Concern (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence - no.09003. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Project Summary - no.09003. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - no.09003. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Progress Report - no.09003. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Far (Box 67, Folder 5-8)
    - Correspondence - no.09004. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Project Summary - no.09004. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - no.09004. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Progress Report - no.09004. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - C.A.R.E. (Box 67, Folder 9-12)
    - Project Summary - no.09005. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - no.09005. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - no.09005. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Progress Report - no.09005. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Swedish-Sudanese Association (Box 67, Folder 13-17)
    - Unfoldered material-Integ. development Bara. Kordofan - no.09006. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - no.09006. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - no.09006. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Project Summary - no.09006. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Progress Report - no.09006. (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Adventist Development and Relief Agency (ADRA) (Box 67, Folder 18-25)
    - Correspondence - no.09007. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - no.09007. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Project Summary - no.09007. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Progress Report - no.09007. (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - no.09008. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Project Summary - no.09008. (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - no.09008. (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Progress Report - no.09008. (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Sudan / Angola, 1985-1990
  - Plan Sudan (Box 68, Folder 1-8)
    - Correspondence - 09009. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 09009. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 09009. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - 09009. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 09010. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 09010. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 09010. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Progress report - 09010. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Save the Children/Sudan (Box 68, Folder 9, 11-12)
    - Correspondence - 09011. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 09011. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 09011. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. (Box 68, Folder 10, 13-20)
    - Progress report - 09011. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - 09012. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 09012. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 09012. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Progress report - 09012. (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 09013. (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Project summary - 09013. (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 09013. (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Progress report - 09013. (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - International Voluntary Welfare (Box 68, Box 69)
    - Correspondence - 09014. (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 09014. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Financial information - 09014. (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Progress report - 09014. (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - 09015. (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Financial information - 09015. (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Project summary - 09015. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Progress report - 09015. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Sudan (Box 69, Folder 3-16)
    - R&RR - General. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - United Nations letter & list - R&RR. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) - R&RR. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - R&RR - EPI - 09102 - 09104. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - R&RR - Save the Children - Save the Children Fund (SCF)/UK - 09103. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - R&RR - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees - C.L.D.C.H. - 09104. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees - R&RR - 09105. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - R&RR - U.N.I.C.E.F. - 09107. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - R&RR - Interaction/Office of Equal Opportunity and Access - WFP/Port - 09109. (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees - R&RR - 09110. (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - R&RR - World Vision - 09113. (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations. (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Country background. (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Angola (Box 69, Folder 17-20)
    - Emergency funds - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Country background. (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Ajuda de Desenvolvimento de Povo para Povo (ADPP) (Box 69, Folder 21-23)
    - Correspondence - no.10701. (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - no.10701. (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Progress reports - no.10701. (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Sudan / Angola / Mauri, 1985-1990
  - R&RR - Report - Africare. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Mauritania (Box 70, Folder 2-6)
    - Emergency funds - General - R&RR. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Emergency funds - Terre des Hommes - R&RR - 05103. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Emergency funds - R&RR - Terre des Hommes - Report - 05103. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - R&RR - United Nations Development Programme - 05104. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - M.S.F. - 05201. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Helen Keller International (Box 70, Folder 7-10)
    - Correspondence - 05301. (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 05301. (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Budget - 05301. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Reports - 05301. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - C.A.R.T.A.S. (Box 70, Folder 11-13)
    - Correspondence - 05001. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Financial information - 05001. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Project summary - 05001. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - M.S.F. (Box 70, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence - 05002. (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 05002. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 05002. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - U.N.D.-I.L.O. (Box 70, Folder 17-19)
    - Correspondence - 05003. (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 05003. (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - 05003. (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - United Nations Development Programme/F.A.O. (Box 70, Folder 20-22)
    - Correspondence - 05004. (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 05004. (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - United Nations Development Programme/F.A.O. - Financial information - 05004. (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Terre des Hommes (Box 70, Folder 23-25)
    - Correspondence - 05402. (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 05402. (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Project summary - 05402. (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded, 1985-1992
  - Association Malienne pour l'Insertion Professionnelle des Jeunes (AMIPJ). (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Agency for Co-operation and Research in Development (ACORD). (Box 209, Folder 25)
  - Africare. (Box 209, Folder 30)
  - Forum of African Voluntary Development Organization. (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - P.A.R.C. (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Balance remaining - Angola (Box 210, Folder 3-11)
    - ACORD - Revised proposals - 10401. (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Euro Action ACORD - correspondence - 10401. (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - ACORD - financial - 10401. (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - project summary - 10403. (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - progress report - 10403. (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - financial - 10403. (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - correspondence - 10403. (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - O.M.A. - correspondence no.2 - 10403. (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - O.M.A. - financial - 10405. (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - C.O.A.R.L.I.P. (Box 210, Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence - 01704. (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Financial - 01704. (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 01704. (Box 210, Folder 14)
  - A.R.P.E.S. (Box 210, Folder 15-17)
    - Correspondence - 02703. (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 12703. (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Financial - 02703. (Box 210, Folder 17)
  - F.M.R.D. (Box 210, Folder 18-21)
    - Correspondence - 03404. (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Financial - 03404. (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Progress report - 03404. (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 03404. (Box 210, Folder 21)
  - Groupe Jeunes (Box 211, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence - 04704. (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 4704. (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Babiker Badri Scientific Association for Women's Studies, Sudan (BBSAWS) (Box 211, Folder 3-6)
    - Financial - 09702. (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 09702. (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - 09702. (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Project reports - 09702. (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Sudan Council of Churches (Box 211, Folder 7-10)
    - Project summary - 09R06. (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - 09R06. (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Progress reports - 09R06. (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Financial - 09R06. (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - I.A.G. 01. (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Narrative guidelines report (English). (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - O.M.A.E.S. - correspondence - 04R01b. (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Oxfam 01-06. (Box 211, Folder 14-19)
  - Oxfam/U.S. 07 EMG. (Box 211, Folder 20)
  - Association pour la Promotion de la Femme Sngalaise (APROFES). (Box 211, Folder 21)
  - A.S.H.O.K.A. (Box 211, Folder 22)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) no.102. (Box 211, Folder 23)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) no.101. (Box 211, Folder 24)
  - Releif and Rehabilitation Commission. (Box 211, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 211, Folder 26)
  - Relief and rapid response - billing and report form. (Box 211, Folder 27)
  - Various applications & rejection / acceptance letters. (Box 211, Folder 28)
  - Various master copies - various concept paper / proposal forms. (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Forms (Box 212, Folder 2-5)
    - Financial report (French). (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Financial report (Portuguese). (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Financial report (English). (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Gift certificates. (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Mailing labels - Program Review Board. (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - Housing programs. (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - U.S.A. for Africa workshop. (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Center for Documentary Media. (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Visa applications. (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Mission statement & reports. (Box 212, Folder 11)
  - Standard forms. (Box 212, Folder 12)
  - Field trips. (Box 212, Folder 13)
  - D.A.R.N.A. - Chad. (Box 212, Folder 14)
  - Ministry of Health / Maputo Central Hospital - Mozambique. (Box 212, Folder 15)
  - U.S.A. for Africa end of program. (Box 212, Folder 16)
  - U.S.A. - Globalvision / Southern Africa. (Box 212, Folder 17)
  - University of Rochester (Box 213, Folder 1-4)
    - MCH Project Mali (continues MTF). (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Financial - 04708. (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 04708. (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 04708. (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Groupe Jeunes - financial - 04704. (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Doulous (Box 213, Folder 6-8)
    - Project summary - 05402. (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - 05402. (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Financial - 05402. (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Mozambique Anglican Church - proformas - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Diocese dos Limbombos (Box 213, Folder 10-14)
    - Correspondence no.1 - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence no.2 - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Mozambique food production - correspondence no.3 - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Project reports - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 06404. (Box 213, Folder 14)
  - SAGE: A Scholarly Journal on Black Women (vol.7, no.1)., 1990 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Diocese dos Libombos - financial - 06404. (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Community Aid Abroad (Box 214, Folder 3-6)
    - Progress reports - 06702. (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 06702. (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Financial - 06702. (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 06702. (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Community Aid Abroad / Inhambane (Box 214, Folder 7-10)
    - Project reports - 06R03. (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - 06R03. (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Financial - 06R03. (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - 06R03. (Box 214, Folder 10)
  - Eduardo Mondlane University (Mozambique) Faculty of Medicine / Harlem Medical Center (Box 214, Folder 11-14)
    - Project summary - 06709. (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Project reports - 06709. (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - 06709. (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Financial - 06709. (Box 214, Folder 14)
  - A.R.P.N. (Box 214, Folder 15-17)
    - Correspondence - 07702. (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Financial - 07702. (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Project summary. (Box 214, Folder 17)
  - Tango organizations - Gambia (Box 215, Folder 1-3)
    - Project summary - 08408. (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 08408. (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Financial - 08408. (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Forum des Organisations Volontaires Africaines de Dveloppement (FOVAD) / Senegal (C.O.V.O.D.E.S.) (Box 215, Folder 4-6)
    - Financial - 08711. (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 08711. (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 08711. (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - E.C.S.D. (Box 215, Folder 7-11)
    - Correspondence - 09403. (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Project reports - 09403. (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - 09403. (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Financial - 09403. (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Program report for 1989 - 09403. (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - Comite de Coordination des Actions des Organisations non Governementales (CCA-ONG) - Mali. (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Conseil des Organisations non Governementales d'Appui au Developpement (CONGAD). (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Council of Churches of Nambia. (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Country Woman Association of Nigeria (COWAN). (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Development Group for Alternative Policies, Incorporated. (Box 216, Folder 5)